so just getting into a slow start
所以刚开始很慢
because we're hoping that we will have a
因为我们希望我们有一个
few more people Dharma in and we have
佛法的人很少，我们有
Alessia and Edwin here and then we have
Alessia和Edwin在这里，然后我们有了
ad brought home whites pullback Shabnam
广告带回家白人回调Shabnam
al and myself we are all very busy or
我和我自己都很忙
the community rather is extremely busy
社区非常忙
with some preparing for the Jakarta 8
一些为雅加达8做准备
release so today we wanted just to give
发布，所以今天我们只想给
a quick update on where we're at and
快速了解我们的位置和
talk about some major event events that
谈论一些重大事件
we're planning and that are related to
我们正在计划，并且与
very much related to and focused on
与……密切相关
Jakarta 8 and and wrap up the call with
雅加达8并结束通话
that so we will start with Ed Brad who
所以我们将从埃德·布拉德开始
is on the west coast and yeah and if you
在西海岸，是的，如果你
want to take it over that would be great
想要接管那将很棒
I'll stop sharing on my hand
我将不再分享
they are great thank you all right I
他们很好，谢谢你，我
apologize for not turning on the video
抱歉未打开视频
it seems to suck the bandwidth out a
似乎在吸收带宽
mile
英里
poor little laptop so I don't know maybe
可怜的小笔记本电脑，所以我也许不知道
if I was some if I got rid of more stuff
如果我能摆脱更多的东西
moaning let's see if I can get this
an吟着，让我看看我能不能得到这个
going here all right that didn't do what
去这里没事的没事
I wanted whatever okay okay so I get to
我想要任何可以的东西，所以我可以
give you the project management stuff
给你项目管理的东西
which is sort of like oh my god more
有点像我的天哪
product management I was thinking about
我正在考虑的产品管理
this as I was trying to put this
正如我试图把这个
together last couple days so we're on
最后几天在一起，所以我们在
track for delivering all jacquard ee8
交付所有提花ee8的轨道
specifications just in case anybody has
规格以防万一有人
any question about it um we should I'm I
关于这个的任何问题，我们应该是我
believe we are on track for delivering
相信我们在实现目标
this corner the full this will include
这个角落，这将包括完整
the full text of the platform full
平台全文全文
profile and web profiles specifications
配置文件和Web配置文件规范
and then we have a reviewed text
然后我们有一个评论文本
javadocs and revived api jars for all
javadocs和复兴的api jars
the rest of the components that go on
其余的其余部分
which car de8 that just in itself was
哪一辆车本身就是
isn't required a lot of coordination a
不需要很多协调
lot of community effort
很多社区的努力
and a lot of work by a lot of people so
还有很多人的很多工作
I'm salted into this presentation a few
我沉迷于这个演讲中
names I don't want anybody to feel like
我不想让任何人都喜欢的名字
I'm sliding them these are just a few
我给他们滑动这些只是几个
people that that I chose to pick out of
我选择挑选出来的人
the crowds here and and if I you know if
这里的人群，如果我你知道的话
you feel like you did a lot of work and
你觉得自己做了很多工作，
I didn't mention you I apologize in
我没有提到你，我道歉
advance for that so each specification
为此，每个规格
will consist of a it's document an API
将包含一个文档API
release which will be a binary jar Java
发布将是一个二进制jar Java
Docs and the source code will consist of
文档和源代码将包括
a TCK and a verification of a compatible
TCK和兼容证明
implementation and this is all delivered
实施，这一切都已交付
under the GNU jacquard ee8 specification
在GNU提花ee8规范下
process sorry sukar de specification
处理对不起，sukar de规范
process in terms of building out all
建立全部流程
these technologies a few names came to
这些技术有几个名字
mind for people that you know I think
介意那些你知道我想的人
really I wouldn't that we wouldn't have
真的，我不会，我们不会
been able to to accomplish this I not
能够做到这一点，我没有
sure I spelled Steve name right but
确定我拼写了史蒂夫的名字，但是
anyway
无论如何
Demetri Steve Ivar on jana pol really
Demetri Steve Ivar在Jana Pol上
you know they helped pull a lot of
你知道他们帮助拉了很多
things together from you know various
在一起的事情你知道各种各样
panics annex that we that occurred along
我们发生的恐慌附件
the way in terms of the specification
规格方面的方式
process I think it was touch-and-go but
我认为这是一触即发的过程，但是
we are on track to have those all
我们有望拥有所有这些
released this quarter the ballots for
发布了本季度的选票
all specifications are currently running
目前正在运行所有规格
at least that's what I was told I didn't
至少我被告知我没有
actually go check it but I'm trusting
实际上去检查它，但我相信
that I was represented correctly to me
正确地代表我
and if anybody is interested in watching
如果有人有兴趣观看
you know or sort of observing the
你知道或观察
balloting I'm sure it's dull but you can
投票我确定这很乏味，但您可以
join this some public list card or not
是否加入此公共列表卡
EEE - spec at eclipse.org and then I
EEE-规格在eclipse.org，然后我
also include the the URL for it and you
还包括它的URL，您
can subscribe to that list
可以订阅该列表
if anybody posts you know their ballots
如果有人发布您知道他们的选票
with questions or with comments or
有问题或评论或
whatever the specification themselves
不管规格本身
will become available at the GRT
将在GRT提供
specifications website that this I
我这个规格网站
wanted to show this but unfortunately
想要显示这个，但不幸的是
there isn't much there right now except
除了那里，现在没有什么了
some you know some templating work so I
有些你知道一些模板工作，所以我
think just bookmark that we can't
认为只是书签，我们不能
actually publish them until the ballots
实际发布到选票发布
are approved so you know stay tuned like
被批准，所以你知道保持关注
the last ballots started yesterday and
昨天的最后一次投票开始了，
the battle period is two weeks so look
战斗期是两个星期，所以
for a lot of activity as soon as these
这些就可以进行很多活动
ballots start completing their ballot
选票开始完成他们的选票
duration let's see I will release
持续时间，让我们看看我会释放
eclipse plasters 5.1 well actually we're
蚀膏药5.1其实我们是
not gonna release it we will certify
不会发布它，我们将证明
that Eclipse classes 5.1 in a full and
Eclipse将5.1完整地
web profile is qualified as a compatible
网页配置文件符合兼容条件
implementation and what that platform so
实施以及该平台是什么
this I can fix this right here maybe I
我可以在这里解决这个问题，也许我
can fix those rater compatible
可以修复那些与评级者兼容的问题
implementation platforms and I think
实现平台，我认为
they're I'm told that there are other
他们被告知，还有其他
implementations in the works I don't
我没有的作品中的实现
want to steal anybody's thunder but do
想偷别人的雷声但是
watch for announcements I suspect that
注意公告，我怀疑
there will be um you know some other
会有你知道
products that will jump in as soon as
产品将尽快进入
the either just wild ballots or our
要么是野蛮的选票，要么是我们的
closing or shortly thereafter with their
结束或不久之后与他们
announcements about their projects and
关于他们的项目的公告以及
products this couldn't have been done
无法做到的产品
without a lot you know the entire
没有很多，你知道整个
community was really sort of focusing on
社区真的有点专注于
this right this is all the specification
这是所有规格
work three days a week working on the
每周工作三天
specification committee extra meetings
规格委员会额外会议
for project planning all just my inbox
仅用于我的收件箱的项目计划
is just destroyed with all in all this
在这一切中被摧毁了
in email about you know this or that or
在关于您的电子邮件中知道这个或那个或
these questions or these things that
这些问题或这些东西
need to be fixed thank you to David
需要解决，谢谢大卫
Blevins to Scott stark Bill Shannon are
斯科特·史塔克·比尔·香农（Bill Shannon）
John and Kevin Sutter
约翰和凯文·萨特
I think for me the thing that I'm most
我觉得对我来说最重要的是
proud about this is you know these guys
为此感到骄傲的是你知道这些家伙
did a lot of work and they're you know
做了很多工作，他们是你知道的
it's not Oracle Oracle Oracle on this
这不是Oracle Oracle Oracle
list you know so that was really you
列出你知道的，所以那真的是你
know
知道
our goal was to get the community
我们的目标是建立社区
engaged with this and right now that's
从事这个，现在就是
all looking pretty good I'm you know I'm
看起来都不错我是你知道我是
very thankful for all the work that
非常感谢所有的工作
these people have done and and everybody
这些人都做了，每个人
else you know and I just again I'm just
否则你知道，我只是我只是
pulling out some people that I think
拉出一些我认为的人
we're particularly vocal or or struck me
我们特别发声或打动我
as doing work this is pretty much the
做工作这几乎是
same slide as last month you know what's
与上个月相同的幻灯片，您知道这是什么
in the TCK bundle right it contains a
在TCK套件中，它包含一个
TCK it contains a bunch of documentation
TCK它包含大量文档
and it also contains an exclude list we
并且还包含一个排除列表
you know we we will publish all of these
你知道我们将发布所有这些
under the specifications section of each
在每个规格部分下
Carnegie website and these will be
卡内基网站，这些将是
become the normative tcks
成为规范
for everybody to use moving forward for
供大家使用
the duration of for as long as Shekhar
持续时间长达Shekhar
DEA lives new specifications will be
DEA生活的新规范将是
coming out and eventually they will find
出来，最终他们会发现
their way to this to this specification
他们对此规范的方式
site so if you look at the pull requests
网站，因此，如果您查看请求请求
I think there's 73 outstanding pull
我认为有73个出色的吸引力
requests there's two for every
要求每个都有两个
specification so and I said there's a
规格，所以我说有一个
point workout right but I think there's
正确的点运动，但我认为
a few extra PRS in here but you know
这里有一些额外的PRS，但您知道
that's a lot to keep track of you know
可以让您知道很多
and hats off to the community for
并向社区致敬
managing to get all these things done
设法完成所有这些事情
for managing to keep track of all of
用于跟踪所有
them and and and you know even finding
他们和，你知道甚至发现
the ones oh crap we forgot about this we
那些废话，我们忘记了这一点，我们
forgot about that you know it's uh we
忘记了你知道这是我们
managed to I think we've managed to pull
我想我们已经设法拉
it off I hope I'm not you know jumping
我希望我不是你知道跳
to a conclusion yet um a couple things
得出结论，但还有几件事
about the TCK setup right les TC gays
关于TCK设置对TC同性恋
themselves last month I had a couple of
自己上个月我有几个
links about how to use how you can
有关如何使用方法的链接
actually set up the tcks I did want to
实际设置了我确实想要的tcks
kind of show you you know in case you're
如果你知道的话，你会知道
actually using TCS or looking at any of
实际使用TCS或查看任何
the work that we've done when you're
您在工作时我们所做的工作
looking at the TC
看TC
Caze right I just brought this up as an
没错，我只是提出来
example this is the test runner that
例如，这是测试跑步者
runs the standalone TCK is for all of
运行独立的TCK适用于所有
the Eclipse GlassFish 55.1 and what you
Eclipse GlassFish 55.1和您
can see is we basically run a build
可以看到，我们基本上是运行构建
that's what this little build check
这就是这个小小的构建检查
marks here and then we paralyze all of
在这里标记，然后我们瘫痪所有
these TC these standalone T CK's and run
这些TC这些独立的T CK并运行
them essentially we allow the the
他们基本上我们允许
Jenkins job manager to to run these all
詹金斯的工作经理来运行所有这些
in parallel so one of the things that
并行的事情之一就是
you might say is well ok great what do I
你可能会说很好，很好，我该怎么办
do I actually figured out what got run
我真的想通了什么吗
well you select you can select any of
好吧，您可以选择任何一个
these TCK names and you know we elected
这些TCK名称，你知道我们当选
early on in this project not to change
在这个项目的早期不要改变
any of the names from what they were
他们名字中的任何一个
before but that'll be something we can
以前，但是那是我们可以做的
do in the next prize in the next cycle
在下一个周期中获得下一个奖项
and you can actually look at the test
您实际上可以查看测试
output it's not very exciting but if
输出不是很令人兴奋，但是如果
you're trying to debug something if you
您正在尝试调试某些东西，如果您
look at the complete log I'm not going
看我不去的完整日志
to bore you with that right now but if
现在让您感到厌烦，但是如果
you look at the complete log you can see
你看完整的日志，你可以看到
that the they you can see where all the
他们可以看到所有
tests are they're run you can't really
测试他们正在运行，你真的不能
just sort of say ok oh look an exception
只是说好吧，哦，看起来很特别
that must be an error that's not the way
那一定是错误的方式
to interpret the test because a lot of
解释测试，因为很多
times the tests are testing did an
次测试正在测试
exception occur right you can look at
异常发生的权利，你可以看看
the logs and you can use those to
日志，您可以使用这些日志
diagnose problems if you're you know if
如果您知道，请诊断问题
you're if you want to see what how that
如果你想看看那是怎么回事
test worked and and what was the you
测试成功了，你是什么
know what were problems that someone's
知道某人的问题是什么
complaining about in addition you know
抱怨另外你知道
you can use the same tool and run
您可以使用相同的工具并运行
subsets so right here's the same test
子集，所以这里是相同的测试
run or running but we only selected a
运行或运行，但我们只选择了一个
few tests to run in this this particular
在此特定条件下运行的测试很少
example where these are some tests that
这些是一些测试的示例
we noticed some oops is in that we had
我们注意到有些糟糕之处在于
to rerun late in the game all right so
可以在游戏后期重新运行，这样
so anyway these are valuable tools I put
所以无论如何，这些都是我投入的宝贵工具
the links in the presentation the
演示文稿中的链接
presentation is here in the Jakara de
演示在Jakara de
august 2019 community update so you
2019年8月社区更新，因此您
should be able to find you know get back
应该能够找到你知道的回来
to these references if you need the
这些参考，如果您需要
we couldn't have done this without some
没有一些我们不可能做到这一点
assistance from our other team here at
来自我们其他团队的协助
Oracle I'll mention but he you know he
我会提甲骨文，但他你知道他
was what the original sort of leader of
原来是那种领导者
the team that was some moving these all
那些动了所有这些的团队
from internal Oracle systems to external
从内部Oracle系统到外部
systems running at Jenkins and then most
系统运行在詹金斯，然后大多数
recently I went Joseph anon keychain and
最近我去了约瑟夫（Joseph anon）钥匙扣，
a couple other people out of our IDC
我们IDC中的其他几个人
office have been very instrumental in
办公室在
and getting these things done and thank
完成这些事情，谢谢
you to everybody in the community who
您对社区中的每个人
looked at the tests who tried to run
看了谁尝试运行的测试
them who's you know struggled with why
你认识的人为之苦恼
can't I get this test to work and what
我不能让该测试正常工作吗？
is that thing I have to download to all
那是我必须下载到所有的东西吗
those people who gave us feedback and
那些给我们反馈的人
helped strengthen the way these work
帮助加强了这些工作的方式
we're not done with that right we we can
我们还没有做到这一点，我们可以
make we can always do better on all of
使我们始终可以在所有方面做得更好
this but thank you thank you thank you
这个但是谢谢谢谢谢谢
alright so what's next right after the
好吧，那么接下来的下一步是什么
ballots close you'll see a bunch of a
选票关闭，您会看到一堆
small handful of specifications that
一小部分规格
will come through I think it's these
会通过我认为这是这些
four here these are specifications that
这是四个规格
are not required for jakar de-age but
不需要雅加尔衰老，但
they will be needed when we start moving
当我们开始移动时将需要它们
off of java SE 8 because they've been
之所以脱离Java SE 8，是因为它们
deprecated out of java SE so you'll see
Java SE已弃用，因此您将看到
some additional material coming from the
一些额外的材料来自
coming to the specification community to
进入规范社区
basically bring these into the jacquard
基本上把这些提花
ee specification process so it's card
ee规格说明
activation soap with attachments XML Web
带有附件的激活肥皂XML Web
Services and XML bindings let's see so I
服务和XML绑定让我们来看一下
was intending to show this with the in
打算用in显示
presentation mode and anyone see this
演示模式，任何人都可以看到
stupid blue thing around but so I
周围是愚蠢的蓝色东西，但我
apologize for the way it looks but oh
为它的外观道歉，但是哦
well there you go
好吧，你去
so remember we didn't rerelease
所以记住我们没有释放
GlassFish right and that's because we're
GlassFish对，那是因为我们
trying to prove the goal that you can
试图证明目标，你可以
take an existing Java EE a certified
取得现有Java EE认证
product and recertified it with some
产品并通过一些认证
already no changes and and I'm apply for
已经没有变化，我正在申请
certification under jacquard EEE we have
提花EEE认证
accomplished this goal with the clips
通过剪辑实现了这一目标
GlassFish we hope to see replication of
我们希望GlassFish能够复制
that result with additional products but
与其他产品的结果，但
that was a key goal that's why there's
那是一个关键目标，这就是为什么
no new glass fifty-five plasters five
没有新的玻璃五十五膏药五
something right
对的东西
we can now start working on new features
我们现在可以开始开发新功能
right so there will be there are already
对，所以已经有
some new specifications I thought I had
我认为我有一些新规格
that up here somewhere
在某处
you know I'm clicking around on things
你知道我在四处点击
so if you go and look at the if you if
所以如果你去看看如果
you and look at the jacquard ee
你看看提花ee
specifications i sorry that the e4j list
规格，我很抱歉e4j列表
of all the projects all the sub projects
在所有项目中所有子项目
you'll see several projects in there
你会在那里看到几个项目
that are not part of Jakarta ee8 and
不属于Jakarta ee8的部分，
those will start to come to fruition and
这些将开始实现，
we'll start bringing those into new
我们将开始将它们带入新的领域
versions of of jacquard EEE so start
提花EEE版本开始
thinking about what it is you want right
想着你想要什么
what what is it that people in this
人们在这是什么
community are interested in in moving
社区有兴趣搬家
you know in adding to Jakarta maybe
你知道添加到雅加达
there's not maybe it's not new
也许不是新的
specifications maybe you want to help
规格也许你想帮忙
you like I can't believe how complicated
你喜欢我不敢相信有多么复杂
it is to do you know pick your thing
那是你知道选你的东西吗
right like to simplify that it's time to
想要简化，是时候
start thinking about what those
开始考虑那些
suggestions would be so that we could
建议是这样，我们可以
start bringing those some bringing those
开始带来那些带来那些
projects online so just to sort of wrap
在线上进行项目，以便整理一下
up things that you can watch right of
你可以看的东西
course you can still subscribe you can
当然您仍然可以订阅
watch all the github any of the github
观看所有github中的所有github
projects that have technologies you're
具有您所需要技术的项目
interested in keep track of if you want
有兴趣跟踪是否需要
to see what's going on in the you know
看看你知道发生了什么
the jacquard EEE website development you
提花EEE网站开发
can keep you can watch the any of the
可以让你可以观看任何
projects under jacquard EEE at github
提花EEE下的项目在github
comms last card EEE there's plenty of
通讯最后一张卡片EEE有很多
mailing lists at that I suggested you
我建议您的邮件列表
subscribe to last month you know I hope
订阅上个月，你知道我希望
people are using that resource
人们正在使用该资源
I mentioned the PRS I already showed you
我提到我已经向您展示的PRS
that
那
list if you want to watch the ballots I
列出你是否想看我的选票
don't know maybe that's like watching
不知道那就像看
grass grow but you can subscribe to this
草长出，但是你可以订阅这个
list it is public and all the all the
列出它是公开的，所有
ballot all the voting is being done in a
投票，所有投票都在
public open forum and you know what can
公开论坛，你知道可以
you help us with right okay you don't
您可以帮助我们，好吧，您不
have to be a developer you know Java
必须成为您知道Java的开发人员
coder right we still need help with
编码员，我们仍然需要帮助
Jakarta websites I guess I would say
雅加达网站，我想我会说
probably less than half of the grd EE
大概不到grd EE的一半
projects you know the the github
您知道github的项目
projects actually have a an informative
项目实际上具有丰富的信息
website there's a lot of work to do
网站上有很多工作要做
there to help bring other community
在那里帮助带来其他社区
members up to speed about what is this
成员加快了解这是什么
project what is it here and how does it
项目在这里是什么以及如何做
you know how do you how would I use it
你知道你将如何使用它
have you you know if you have an
你知道你是否有一个
opportunity to try out any of the
有机会尝试任何
tutorials or any of the sample code yeah
教程或任何示例代码
please we need people to help us
请我们需要人来帮助我们
diagnose those you know that work and
诊断那些你知道的工作，
you know maybe figure out how to make it
你知道也许想出办法
simpler so more people can can access
更简单，以便更多人可以访问
Jakarta II know so file bugs maybe try
雅加达II知道所以可以尝试文件错误
fixing something you know submit a PR
解决您知道的问题，提交公关
and you know see you fast try see if you
你知道很快见到你，看看你是否
can work with the community in that
可以与社区合作
technology and and actually um you know
技术，实际上你知道
I helped improve the component itself
我帮助改善了组件本身
the good news is now we're done with
好消息是我们已经完成了
them we're we're on the cusp of
他们我们正处于风口浪尖
finishing with Jakarta e8 it's time to
完成雅加达e8的时间了
start thinking about what's after that I
开始思考之后我会发生什么
think that's all I got Tania if anybody
认为这就是我得到塔尼亚（Tania）的全部
has questions comment somebody else they
有问题要评论别人
want also my dad yeah go ahead
还希望我爸爸继续
questions comments it is I have a few
问题评论是我有几个
questions it's good to hear that
听到这很高兴
everything is on track for the release
一切都按计划进行
of Jakarta a this quarter but does it
雅加达一个季度，但做到了
still mean that it is going to be
仍然意味着它将是
completely for Jakarta one that is the
完全是针对雅加达的
goal
目标
yeah but is that the same as this
是的，但与此相同
quarter did you mean that
四分之一的意思是
I believe that we are on track to
我相信我们正朝着
complete before jacquard oh and the
在提花之前完成哦
online streaming event that's what
在线流媒体活动就是这样
you're talking about
你在说
yeah accidently but they also secure yes
是的，但他们也确保了
if you meant that so thanks
如果你是那样的话，谢谢
Enid we do mean we people really worked
恩尼德（Enid）我们确实意味着我们的员工确实在工作
hard to try to make that deadline I know
努力去做我知道的最后期限
but I can't guarantee it because there's
但我不能保证，因为有
nothing like you know some some you know
没有像你知道的一些你知道的
p1 problem jumps up but that is our goal
p1问题激增，但这是我们的目标
and we are we still are on track all
而且我们仍然在所有轨道上
right
对
second question in the posture has been
姿势中的第二个问题是
talked about the cost fish fight o2
谈到鱼搏斗O2的成本
released with the new AP ice but you
与新的AP冰一起发布，但是您
know you're now saying that's not going
知道你现在在说那不会
to be necessary I didn't say it's not
有必要，我没有说不是
necessary for Jakarta ee8 but we we do
Jakarta ee8必需的，但我们
you know we that is something that we
你知道我们那是我们
can deliver right we don't need it for
可以提供我们不需要的权利
ee8 that's the main point I'm trying to
ee8是我要尝试的重点
make care right but that you know once
照顾得好，但是你知道一次
we're past the Jakarta ee8 you know
我们过去了，雅加达EE8
hurdle we can do a 5.2 with you know as
我们可以与您一起完成5.2
long as it passes all the compatibility
只要通过所有兼容性
requirements we can make new releases
要求我们可以发布新版本
okay thanks Jatin okay anybody else okay
好，谢谢贾廷，其他人也好
thank you very much ed um so I think on
非常感谢你，所以我想
our agenda the next item is update from
我们的议程下一个项目是从
Shabnam so I will for some marketing
Shabnam，所以我会做一些营销
activities so I will ask
活动，所以我会问
you can see my screen right yeah yeah we
你可以看到我的屏幕吗，是的，我们
can see your creeper so there are a
可以看到你的爬行者，所以有一个
number of activities that we are going
我们要进行的活动数量
to do on communities we have to
在必须要做的社区上做
celebrate the release and also recognize
庆祝发行并认识到
the community's effort around this
社区为此所做的努力
release so we are going to issue a press
发布，所以我们要发布新闻
release on September 10th that will
9月10日发布
recognize dedicated committee members
认可专门委员会成员
vendors and everyone who has come
供应商和每个来的人
together to make this happen so we plan
共同实现这一目标，因此我们计划
to promote certified Jakarta ee8
推广认证的雅加达ee8
compatible implementations which we
我们兼容的实现
expect to be GlassFish 5.1 and other may
期望是GlassFish 5.1，其他可能
be other compatible implementations so
是其他兼容的实现，所以
watch out for announcements and we are
当心公告，我们
also working on a page in Jakarta
也正在雅加达的页面上工作
Jakarta that EE is going to be a hub for
雅加达认为EE将成为
the community to get all information and
社区获取所有信息，以及
updates about everything related
有关所有相关内容的更新
apartment ye so this is a preview but
是的，这是一个预览，但
it's a work in progress so it will link
这是一项正在进行的工作，因此它将链接
to specifications compatible products
符合规格的兼容产品
and over time you will add video
随着时间的流逝，您将添加视频
interviews with the community members
社区成员访谈
and also we worked with the leading
而且我们与领导
members of the community to author an
社区成员撰写
ebook fulfilling the vision for open
实现开放愿景的电子书
source cloud native Java that surprise
源云原生Java令人惊讶
community's vision for cloud native Java
社区对云原生Java的愿景
the significance of this event in
此事件的重要性
releasing Jakarta EA and also provides
发行Jakarta EA，并提供
committees perspective of the future of
委员会对未来的看法
cloud native Java collaboration and also
云原生Java协作以及
at this point of time between eclipse
在日食之间的这个时间点
foundation ourselves and the community
为自己和社区奠定基础
we are expecting between 10 to 20 blogs
我们预计会有10到20个博客
that they go out on September 10th and
他们在9月10日外出
thereafter and echoes foundation is also
此后，呼应的基础也是
going to have a strong presence
将有一个强大的存在
representing Jakarta EE
代表雅加达EE
micro profile and other part projects at
微型轮廓和其他零件项目
code one we are going to be at booth 3 2
我们将在3号展位的代码1 2
to 8 we encourage of
到8我们鼓励
the community to committee members to
社区成员
come and visit us there and we are also
来那里拜访我们，我们也
planning to have a cloud native Java
计划拥有云原生Java
coming in reception at code Vaughn on
在代码Vaughn上接受接待
September 17 to mark the celebration of
9月17日是庆祝活动
Jakarta eh release and also recognize
雅加达eh发布并认识到
the communities there first around micro
首先是微周围的社区
profile so we will update you once we
个人资料，以便我们更新您之后
have more information about this to
有关此的更多信息
share right all right so I think that is
好吧，我认为那是
it okay so let me just on my end I want
好的，所以我就想结束
to provide update on the Jakarta one
提供有关雅加达的最新消息
live stream as well as a little bit on
直播以及一点点
Eclipse con Europe and particularly with
Eclipse con欧洲，尤其是与
regards to community related events so
关于社区相关事件
moving into just a short update on this
对此进行简短的更新
Jakarta one live stream as I hope
我希望雅加达有一场直播
everyone knows is planned for the
大家都知道计划
September 10th we're still looking for
9月10日，我们仍在寻找
people to register and registration is
人要注册，注册是
open I'm showing the the site here it's
打开，我在这里显示网站
really easy to register so please have a
真的很容易注册，所以请
look right now I just want to point out
现在看，我只想指出
that we're close to 500 registered
我们已经接近500个注册
attendees so that is really exciting and
参加者，这真的很令人兴奋，
interesting and want to invite everyone
有趣，想邀请所有人
if you see any particular question here
如果您在这里看到任何特定的问题
any particular session here that you
您在这里进行的任何特定会话
would be interested in and you have
会感兴趣，你有
questions with regards to that session
关于那届会议的问题
it would be I would welcome you to
我会欢迎你
observe and to actually post your
观察并实际发布您的
questions and
问题和
ask questions in this section so you
在这部分问问题
know that way we can the the presenters
知道我们可以通过主持人
can answer online or during their
可以在线或在他们的回答
presentation or after the presentation
演讲或演讲后
and so on so hopefully everyone
等等，希望大家
registered for Jakarta one livestream
注册了雅加达直播
and yeah well we'll see you there
是的，我们在那里见
another extremely important event for
另一个极其重要的事件
for us at Eclipse Foundation is Eclipse
对我们而言，Eclipse Foundation是Eclipse
conure ap' we already share the
conure ap'，我们已经分享了
information where it is and we hope that
信息在哪里，我们希望
you all registered booked your
你们所有人都登记了您的
accommodations and and mark your
住宿并标记您的
calendars we're actively working on the
我们正在积极研究的日历
community related events and I just want
社区相关事件，我只想
to quickly show you and here is the link
快速向您展示，这是链接
to the Eclipse sorry for the cloud
Eclipse对云感到抱歉
native community events and the wiki
本地社区事件和Wiki
page there you can see what we're kind
页面在那里，您可以看到我们的友善
of working on and what we would like to
工作以及我们想要做什么
happen on that day so please have a look
发生在那天，所以请看一看
provide us suggestions there is a
向我们提供建议
suggestion section here you can see who
建议部分，您可以查看谁
is involved in organizing this event and
参与组织这次活动
if you are interested to attend please
如果您有兴趣参加，请
let us know and sign up here at the
让我们知道并在此处注册
attendees section of the wiki page we
Wiki页面的与会者部分，我们
would love to know how many people would
很想知道会有多少人
be present there and we would love to
在那里，我们很乐意
make sure that we're ready for for the
确保我们准备好
people to you know prepare the room and
认识的人准备房间并
do all the logistics up front so that is
先做好所有的后勤工作
pretty much everything that I have for
我几乎拥有的一切
the events that were planning in the
在计划中的事件
near future from the Eclipse Foundation
Eclipse Foundation在不久的将来
perspective yeah go ahead please
观点是的，请继续
let go what was so much beneath you
放开你内心深处的一切
I don't think I'm not sure if this is
我不知道这是不是
intended for us to hear but I do hear
打算让我们听到，但我确实听到
someone's talking is there any question
有人在说话有什么问题吗
no I don't think so okay so any other
不，我不认为这样还可以
comments or questions or as we as I was
评论或问题，或者像我一样
saying in my email considering that
考虑到我在电子邮件中说
we're really focusing on work related to
我们真的专注于与
the Jakarta he8 Ramiz we wanted just to
我们想要的雅加达he8 Ramiz
provide a quick update and and give you
提供快速更新并给您
a heads-up on the progress if there are
如有进展，请提前告知
no questions we will close the call at
没问题，我们将在以下时间结束通话
this point and we will talk to you in
这一点，我们将在
the near future okay
不久的将来还可以
so thanks so much everyone and we'll be
非常感谢大家，我们将
in touch thank you for the date think
联系我们，谢谢你的约会
okay see ya
好吧，再见